let's look at the answer to our log
variable quiz
in this code we are using the lock
count lock and it's really an array of
lock that has elements so we are
indexing into the array and getting that
one element of the array and that's our
lock that we lock to access count of l
and then we unlock that log so the
question was what is really this lock
is it just another location in shared
memory so count lock of l really is just
a memory word
or is it a location in some sort of
special synchronization memory so there
is a sort of special memory where this
array of locks is residing or is it that
locks are special variables that we can
refer to like this in code but really
they don't have memory addresses
whatsoever the correct answer here is
that a lock
is just
another location in shared memory so a
lock is a variable just like any other
variable it has a memory address we can
load
to get its value we can store to change
its value and so on so now we will see
what that variable looks like and what
the lock and unlock functions are
supposed to look like